<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HKUCSMSC</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="title_admission">Admission</string>
    <string name="title_newsevents">NewsEvents</string>
    <string name="title_curriculum">Curriculum</string>
    <string name="title_sturesources">Resources</string>

    <string name="about_leaderwelcome">We are living in the era where technology is widely accepted and becomes so commonplace that we doubt how we ever live without it. Mobile is a good prominent example. From businesses to individual consumers, everyone is connected to everyone, everywhere, all the time. Every day we hear of new technological breakthroughs, e.g. self-driving cars, organ-on-a-chip, smart glasses, drones; they are awe-inspiring. To remain in the game, the best IT professionals strive to maintain current knowledge and skills to take on these continual developments.\n\n
    The Master of Science in Computer Science Programme is a comprehensive and challenging graduate programme with three specialisations and one general stream, namely Financial Computing Stream, Cyber Security Stream, Multimedia Computing Stream and General Computer Science Stream, to meet the needs of both industry and business in Asia, and to make the programme more unique among comparable programmes in the region.\n\n
    As you can see from our curriculum, on one hand we have retained the nuts and bolts subjects to lay a strong foundation. But on the other hand, we updated and revised the curriculum continuously as we assess the career trends and needs of our students, and monitor rapid changes in technology developments. For example, hot topics like “fintech”, “blockchain” are included in some of our courses.\n\n
    If you like the holistic approach of our teaching methods and curriculum, please consider enrolling in this established programme in a world-class university.\n\n\n\n
    <b>Dr. K.P. Chow</b>\n <b>Programme Director</b>\n\n\n\n</string>


    <string name="button_info_contact"><b>Contact Us</b></string>
    <string name="button_info"><b>
    The MSc Programme Office\n
        Department of Computer Science\n
        P3-02, Graduate House\n
        The University of Hong Kong</b>\n
    Tel: (852) 3917 1828\n
        Fax: (852) 2547 4442\n
        Email: <a href='msccs@cs.hku.hk'>msccs@cs.hku.hk</a>\n
        Website URL:  <a href='http://www.msc-cs.hku.hk'>http://www.msc-cs.hku.hk</a>\n
        Facebook Page: <a href='https://www.facebook.com/hkumsccs'>https://www.facebook.com/hkumsccs</a>\n
        Office Hours:\n
        Mon-Fri: 9:00am-12:30pm     1:30pm-5:00pm\n
        Sat:     9:00am-12:00pm\n\n\n
    </string>
<string name="about_faculty">The Department of Computer Science is committed to
    high-quality education and training of computing professionals at both the
    undergraduate and postgraduate levels. At the postgraduate level, we offer two taught
    programmes based on coursework, the MSc(CompSc) and the MSc(ECom and IComp), as well as
    the research-based MPhil and PhD programmes.\n\n

The academic staff is active in research and development in a variety of areas including
    databases, parallel and distributed computing, computer networks, computer graphics,
    algorithms and complexity, computer vision, multimedia, software engineering,
    statistical computing, information security and computer forensics, and legal
    aspects of computing. Some of our research results have been applied to the
    development of real software and systems. You will have these researchers as your
    inspiring teachers of the courses in this programme. Here are some of them.
</string>

    <string name="chanhth"><b>Dr. Chan H.T.H.</b>\nPhD (Carnegie Mellon)\n\nField of Research:\nAlgorithms, Combinatorial Optimization, Graphs, Information Networks, Security and Privacy</string>
    <string name="chankp"><b>Dr. Chan K.P.</b>\nPhD (HK)\n\nField of Research:\nPattern Recognition, Chinese Computing, Facial Expression Recognition, Machine Learning</string>
    <string name="benkao"><b>Prof. Kao B.C.M.</b>\nPhD (Princeton)\n\nField of Research:\nDatabase Management Systems, Data Mining, Real-time Systems, Information Retrieval Systems</string>
    <string name="abouthku"><b>The University of Hong Kong</b>\n\nThe University of Hong Kong (HKU), founded in 1911, is the oldest of Hong Kong’s institutions of higher learning.  It was also the alma mater of Dr. Sun Yat-sen, the founder of modern China.\n\n
        HKU, as a pre-eminent international university, seeks to sustain and enhance its excellence as an institution of higher learning through outstanding teaching and world-class research so as to produce well-rounded graduates with lifelong abilities to provide leadership within the societies they serve.\n\n
        HKU has ten faculties, a graduate school and a number of independent centres of studies and learning. In 2016-17, it had a student population of over 27,800, including over 16,100 undergraduates and 11,700 postgraduates, and an academic staff population of around 3,400. Coupled with an active alumni network and generous endowments for programme research and development, HKU is a dynamic and exciting institution. Stepping into Asia’s next century of phenomenal growth.</string>

    <string name="admission_requirements1"><b>Admission Requirements</b>\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements2"><b>Eligibility</b>\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements3">To be eligible for admission to the programmes, a candidate shall satisfy both the University Entrance Requirements and the Programme Entrance Requirements including but not limited to:\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements4"> a.    shall comply with the General Regulations;\n\nb.    shall hold a Bachelor’s degree of this University or a qualification of equivalent standard from this University or another comparable institution accepted for this purpose;\n\nc.    for a candidate who is seeking admission on the basis of a qualification from a university or comparable institution outside Hong Kong of which the language of teaching and/or examination is not English, shall satisfy the University English language requirement applicable to high degrees as prescribed under General Regulation G2(b); and\n\nd.    satisfy the examiners in a qualifying examination if required.</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements5"><b>Regulations</b>\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements6">1. General Regulations of The University</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements7">https://www4.hku.hk/pubunit/drcd/files/pgdr2017-18/genreg.pdf\n\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements8">2. University\'s Regulations for Taught Postgraduate Curricula:\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements9">https://www4.hku.hk/pubunit/drcd/files/pgdr2017-18/tpg-regulations.pdf\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements10">3. Degree Regulations of MSc(CompSc) for students admitted to the curriculum in 2017-2018 and thereafter:\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements11">http://www.msc-cs.hku.hk/Media/Default/RegulationSyllabus/Regulations_MSc_2017-18.pdf\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements12">http://www.msc-cs.hku.hk/Media/Default/RegulationSyllabus/Syllabus_MSc(CompSc)_2018-19.pdf\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements13">English Language Proficiency Requirement\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements14">Applicants who wish to be admitted on the basis of a qualification from a university or comparable institution outside Hong Kong where the language of teaching and/or examination is not English are required to obtain:\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements15">a. a score of 550 or above (paper-based test) or 80 or above (internet-based test) in the Test of English as a Foreign Language (TOEFL).  Applicants who took the TOEFL should request the Educational Testing Service (ETS) to send an official score report to the University directly. For this purpose, the HKU TOEFL code is 9671. Test scores more than two years old will not be accepted; or\n\nb. a minimum overall band of 6 with no subtest lower than 5.5 in the International English Language Testing System (IELTS); or\n\nc. grade C or above in the Overseas General Certificate of Education (GCE); or\n\nd. grade C or above in the International General Certificate of Secondary Education (IGCSE); or\n\ne. grade C or above in the Cambridge Test of Proficiency in English Language;\n</string>
    <string name="admission_requirements16">unless in exceptional circumstances they are exempted from this requirement.\n</string>

    <string name="admission_procedures1"><b>Application Procedures</b></string>
    <string name="admission_procedures2">Applicants can submit their application via the online application system by clicking the following button.\n</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures3">The following supporting documents should be uploaded to the online application system before the application deadline or expiry of your application account (which is valid for four weeks only), whichever is earlier:</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures4">• Graduate transcript(s) with grading system of all tertiary level studies\n\n• Degree certificate(s)\n\n• English Language proficiency test score report, such as TOEFL or IELTS (only for applicants with qualifications from institutions outside Hong Kong where the language of instruction and/or examination is not English)\n\n• Proof of Cumulative Grade Point Average (CGPA) / average grade / average mark\n\n• Official proof of class ranking, if available\n\n• A curriculum vitae (C.V.)</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures5">Applicants are not required to submit original documents during the application stage.  Should an applicant be given an admission offer by the Programme, he/she will receive notification of the need to submit original/certified true copy* of the documents to the MSc(CompSc) Programme Office.\n\nPlease note that documents once submitted will not be returned, and will be destroyed if the application is unsuccessful.\n\n*The University will only ACCEPT originals and copies of the documents that have been duly declared as true copies before a notary public.</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures6">Application Fee\n\n</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures7">The application fee is HK$300 (non-refundable), paid by credit card online.</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures8">Application Timetable\n\n</string>
    <string name="admission_procedures9">To be considered for a round, you must submit a complete application, including all online / mail-in materials by the day of the deadline.\n\nThe results for admission in September are normally available by July of the same year. Hence, applicants who do not hear from the Faculty of Engineering by July 31, 2019 may assume the application to be unsuccessful.\n</string>

    <string name="admission_compositionfees1">Composition Fees\n</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees2">The composition fee for each 6 credit-units in MSc(CompSc) is HK$13,000*.  The dissertation, which is equivalent to 24 credits, has a composition fee of HK$52,000*.  The total composition fees are therefore as follows:\n</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees3">48 credit-units (8 courses) + dissertation:\n(HK$13,000* x 8) + (HK$52,000*) = HK$156,000*\n</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees4">Students who select to study a course from the MSc(ECom and IComp) and MSc(Eng) programmes have to pay HK$13,000* and HK$12,000* respectively per 6-credit course.\n\n* Subject to University approval\n\nFees for enrolled courses are paid on semester basis.  The first instalment of composition fees of 12 credit-units is payable at the time of acceptance of an offer of admission.\n\nGenerally composition fees for cancelled enrolment before specified deadline are not refunded, but can be used to pay for another enrolled course or carried over to the next semester as credit. (Subject to the approval by the University)\n\n</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees5">Financial Assistance\n</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees6"><i>For Hong Kong Residents\n</i></string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees7">Some of our courses have been included in the list of reimbursable courses for the Hong Kong Continuing Education Fund (CEF) which provides reimbursement up to HK$10,000 for eligible local students.  More details available at:</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees8">http://www.wfsfaa.gov.hk/cef/index.htm\n\n</string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees9"><i>For PRC Candidates\n</i></string>
    <string name="admission_compositionfees10">PRC students who have successfully applied and been offered a place in the Master of Science in Computer Science as full-time students in Hong Kong have an opportunity to have their composition fees reduced if they apply and are awarded The China Postgraduate Scholarships for Computer Science.\n\nThe maximum number of scholarships for 2019-20 is thirty, with a maximum value of HK$30,000 each.\n\nThe scholarships shall be used to meet part of the composition fees for a full-time programme of studies leading to the degree of Master of Science in Computer Science.\n\nThe scholarships shall be awarded mainly on the basis of academic merits.7\n</string>

    <string name="admission_informationsessions1">Information Sessions\n</string>
    <string name="admission_informationsessions2">Join us at the information sessions, and find out if the Master of Science in Computer Science Programme is the right fit for your career goals. Information Sessions include a programme overview and Q and A, plus the opportunity to talk informally with Programme Director and staff. Potential applicants are welcome.\n\nInformation sessions will be organized in Hong Kong and Mainland China. Details of these information sessions will be announced on our website and/or advertised online and in major local newspapers.\n\nDetails of the information sessions:\n</string>

    <string name="admission_ourstudents1">Words from Students</string>
    <string name="admission_ourstudents2">When you enrol in the MSc(CompSc) Programme, you gain all the advantages of a famous university with an outstanding reputation. When you leave our Programme, you will have a solid foundation in the theoretical aspect of computer science, together with hands-on technical experience in information technology, to help you begin a rewarding career.\n\nBut a master’s programme does not have to be the last chapter of your learning merely technical, hard-core information technology; it can serve as a springboard to other career opportunities and learning challenges. For example, many of our graduates who find themselves moving into management, may continue their studies towards an MBA degree, while others may go on to doctoral studies here at HKU or elsewhere.\n\nSome of our students and graduates would also like to share their experience with you.\n</string>
    <string name="admission_clarkwords">After studying and working for several years in the United States, I chose to do my Master degree at HKU based on the sterling reputation that the University and the CS programme have around the world. Having the flexibility to design my own studies and select interesting courses as well as having the opportunity to learn from top professors really appealed to me. The coursework was challenging yet fulfilling, and topics were relevant for today fast-changing world. I have been able to work with cutting-edge robotic systems during my dissertation project, and I am excited to begin a new career in the technology field armed with my MSc from HKU.</string>
    <string name="admission_cuiyitongwords">Studying in HKU MSc(CompSc) has prepared me for success in a couple of ways.  First, MSc(CompSc) offers a range of courses tailored to meet the specific academic and professional goals of each student.  Most of the hot topics are involved, such as Machine Learning, Data Mining, Deep Learning, Cloud Computing, Blockchain technology, etc.  When I do job-hunting, I find the courses have really offered help to me down-to-earth.  The programme also gives me much resources of knowledge and job opportunities.  Second, the strict requirements of each course induce me to be hard-working all the time, and provide me with many advanced learning skills.  The teamwork tasks gave me opportunity to know more about my classmates, who are down-to-earth and humble.\n\nCountless sleepless nights in HKU MSc(CompSc)  made me a better person.  It was an incredible experience that I don't think I could have anywhere else.</string>
    <string name="admission_hutianyiwords">In the past year, I benefit a lot from tough courses in this program, which makes up my deficiency in coding experience and brings me edge-cutting knowledge. Meanwhile, the design of four streams helps me concentrate on the study of computational finance. Comparing with programs in other universities, I think numerous opportunities provided by this program is a great advantage. Some teachers are from teaching staff with strong research experience while others are from industry with enrich working experience, meaning that communicating with them positively can bring us extra benefits. Furthermore, thanks to the reputation of the University of Hong Kong, we have access to many competitions, one of which is Rotman International Trading Competition held in Toronto competing with other top universities among the world. Through those competitions, I make friends with experienced algo traders and they also teach me much beyond the book, which enhance my will to work in this industry. \n\nAll in all, this program is really fruitful, and students from different background can get what they want. But the study period is short, I think designing the study plan on first day is important and necessary. Just be open and outgoing, the precious opportunity is around us.</string>
    <string name="admission_leelitongwords">There are a wide range of courses to choose from - AI, cybersecurity and financial computing to name a few. The course contents are up to date and HKU provides quality resources so that the learning process is smooth and unhindered.  The best part about the MSc programme is perhaps the people that you meet - I’ve made many friends with similar interest and drive.  We also have down-to-earth professors who are willing to dedicate time and effort to introduce current concepts and topics relevant to the industry.  On top of having a rigorous and well laid out curriculum, studying at HKU gives me an enjoyable and dynamic student life.  I am able to easily meet people entering or already working in the tech industry and I’m also able to practice and learn both Cantonese and Mandarin due to the diversity of students.  Lastly, Hong Kong provides a fun and safe place to study and is ideally located to immerse oneself into what is perhaps the world’s largest and most sophisticated mecca of technology - the Greater Bay Area."</string>

    <string name="admission_admission_faq1">1. I am an undergraduate student in the final year. Can I apply your programme?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq2">2. What supporting documents are required?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq3">3. Do I need to post the hardcopy of supporting doucments to HKU during application?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq4">4. Are photocopies of the TOEFL or IELTS reports accepted?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq5">5. Do I need to submit a C.V. or a personal statement?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq6">6. Do I need to submit reference letters? Is there any form for referees?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq7">7. I am an applicant from Mainland China. How do I apply the China Postgraduate Scholarships for Computer Science?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq8">8. How many confidential statements from referee are required if I apply the China Postgraduate Scholarships?</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq9">9. When will I know the application results?</string>

    <string name="admission_admission_faq1_answer">You can submit application if you expect that you will complete your current study and obtain official certification on your graduation by August. Non-local students should however note that the official offer letter of admission could be issued only after you have submitted the official certificate on graduation and the complete transcript. This official offer letter is required for your student visa application which will take at least 6 to 8 weeks. Therefore, you may have to reserve enough time for visa application.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq2_answer1">Along with the application the following documents are required to be submitted:</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq2_answer2">1.Graduate transcript(s) with grading system of all tertiary level studies (or interim transcript if graduate transcript is not available yet)\n2.Officially certified degree certificate(s), if available\nEnglish Language proficiency test score report, such as TOEFL or IELTS (only for applicants with qualifications from institutions outside HK where the language of instruction and/or examination is not English)\nProof of Cumulative Grade Point Average (CGPA) / average grade / average mark
If the transcript does not show the cumulative GPA / average grade / average mark, or no school proof is available, please complete calculation sheet (Please use this template to calculate the Cumulative Grade Point Average (CGPA) / average grade / average mark). Instructions can be found at: https://engg.hku.hk/faculty_msc/help.pdf.
5.Official proof of class ranking, if available
6.A curriculum vitae (C.V.)</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq2_answer3">Applicants are NOT required to submit original documents during the application stage. Should an applicant be given an admission offer by the Programme, he/she will receive notification of the need to submit original/certified true copy* of the documents.

* The University will only ACCEPT originals or copies of the documents that have been duly declared as true copies before a notary public (e.g. a Commissioner for Oaths at a City District Office in Hong Kong). Copies of documents may be certified by the appropriate officials of your home institution if you are an overseas applicant. No photocopies will be accepted.

Please note that documents once submitted will not be returned, and will be destroyed if the application is unsuccessful.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq3_answer">Applicants are recommended to provide the softcopy of all supporting documents, which can be uploaded to the on-line application system within 4 weeks after account creation.

Applicants are NOT required to submit original documents during the application stage.

The chance of being admitted are the same even if only softcopy are provided.

Should an applicant be given an admission offer by the Programme, he/she will receive notification of the need to submit original/certified true copy of the documents.

Please note that documents once submitted will not be returned, and will be destroyed if the application is unsuccessful.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq4_answer">Only original test reports are accepted. You could ask the test center to send the official reports directly to HKU.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq5_answer">Yes, you are required to submit a C.V.

Personal statement is optional.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq6_answer">If you are applying the China Postgraduate Scholarships for Computer Science, please refer to question 7 and 8. Otherwise, you do not need to submit reference letters or ask your referees to complete a form at the time of application. The Programme Office will contact you or the referees directly afterwards if reference letters are required.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq7_answer">Application for the Scholarship has to be made together with the application for admission. You need to indicate on the online application system and submit the scholarship application form and the confidential statement from referee by the deadline which is the same as that of admission. The form can be downloaded from the online application system as supporting documents. Any application forms received after the admission result is announced will not be considered.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq8_answer">One confidential statement from referee is required. You can download the form from the online application system.</string>
    <string name="admission_admission_faq9_answer">The admission selection committee works continuously for months to review the large number of applications and to conduct interviews in order to select top candidates for admission to this MSc programme.

Successful applicants will be notified of the result once it is ready.

However, if you have not heard from us by 31 July 2019, you may assume that your application is not successful.</string>

    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq1">1. How to apply for the student visa?</string>
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq2">2. I am a non-local applicant. How do I get information about student visa, finance, accommodation and life in HKU?</string>
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq3">3. If I have a valid work visa or tourist visa, do I need a student visa for studying in Hong Kong?</string>
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq4">4. Can I work in Hong Kong if I am holding a student visa?</string>
<!--
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq1_answer"></string>
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq2_answer"></string>
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq3_answer"></string>
    <string name="admission_visrelated_faq4_answer"></string>
    -->

    <string name="curriculum_courses1">Programme Overview</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses2">The MSc(CompSc) programme is a comprehensive postgraduate study programme provides advanced and in-depth learning in Computer Science.  The programme is credit unit based, with courses of both applied and fundamental nature.\n\nStudents can choose focussed streams of study or a comprehensive and diversified study in Computer Science, i.e. the General Stream.\n\nFocussed streams of study represent a cohesive collection of related courses that provides both fundamental and in-depth exposure to students in a given ICT domain.  Students can extend and deepen their knowledge in the specialization streams in Cyber Security, Multimedia Computing and Financial Computing.\n </string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses3">Stream of Study</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses4">Cyber Security</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses5">The Cyber Security Stream is a multidisciplinary area of study and professional activity concerned with state-of-the-art technology in cyber security. The curriculum covers different aspects of cyber security from different perspectives, including technical, organisational, human-oriented and legal.</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses6">Multimedia Computing</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses7">The Multimedia Computing Stream focuses on multimedia computing, communications, analytics, visualisation and applications.\n\nMultimedia Computing encompasses media coding and processing, streaming-media middleware, media representations, real-time protocols, media analysis, and human-interaction and visualisation techniques.\n\nStudents are encouraged to develop innovative ideas using the latest development in technology such as mobile devices and big-data analytics.\n\n</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses8">Financial Computing</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses9">The Financial Computing Stream is the study of data and algorithms used in finance and the mathematics of computer programs that realise financial models or systems.\n\nFinancial Computing emphasises practical numerical methods and focuses on techniques that are directly applicable to business and financial analysis.\n\nThe emphasis will be in the computing aspect of the financial industry.\n\n</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses10">General Stream</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses11">The General Stream covers a broad, comprehensive range of Computer Science subjects, including a wide range of courses from which students can choose from. It offers students the most flexibility to design their own study portfolio based on their career aspiration or requirements.</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses12">Pattern of Study</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses13">Students are required to complete 72 credits, of which 48 credits from courses (equivalent to eight 6-credit courses) plus a dissertation (equivalent to 24 credits). </string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses14">Selection of Courses</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses15">Students of Cyber Security, Multimedia Computing, or Financial Computing Stream are required to select a minimum of 24 credits of stream specific courses (equivalent to four 6-credit courses) in the corresponding subject group, and undertake a dissertation in the area of the corresponding stream.\n\nFor General Stream, students can choose 48 credits of courses (equivalent to eight 6-credit courses) from any stream and subject group in the curriculum, and undertake a dissertation in any area in computer science.\n\nIn addition to the list of MSc(CompSc) courses for students to choose from, students may select no more than 12 credits of courses (equivalent to two 6-credit courses) from the syllabuses for the degrees of MSc(ECom and IComp) and MSc(Eng), subject to the approval of the Head of the Department of Computer Science.  Details of courses from MSc(ECom and IComp) can be found in this website:\n </string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses16">https://www.ecom-icom.hku.hk</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses17">Capstone Experience – Dissertations</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses18">The capstone experience will definitely be beneficial for students to put together what they have learnt in the programme and demonstrate a deeper understanding of the knowledge they have acquired. Students are required to complete a dissertation (24 credits) and attend some supplementary workshops. The dissertation would represent students’ consolidated capstone experience in their study.</string>
    <string name="curriculum_courses19">Programme Overview</string>

</resources>